[{
       "question":"Who developed Python Programming Language?" ,
       "choice1":"Wick van Rossum" ,
       "choice2":"Rasmus Lerdorf" ,
       "choice3": "Guido van Rossum",
       "choice4":"Niene Stom" ,
       "answer":3

},
   {   
      "question":"What will be the output of the following Python code?\n i = 1 \n while True: \n if i%3 == 0:\n break \n print(i) \n i + = 1",
      "choice1":"1 2 3",
      "choice2":"Error",
      "choice3":"1 2",
      "choice4": "none of the mentioned",
      "answer":2
},
{
     "question":"Python supports the creation of anonymous functions at runtime, using a construct called_____",
      "choice1":"pi",
      "choice2":"anonymous",
      "choice3":"lambda",
      "choice4": "none of the mentioned",
      "answer":3
},
{
     "question":"What will be the output of the following Python code snippet if x=1?",
      "choice1":"4",
      "choice2":"2",
      "choice3":"1",
      "choice4": "8",
      "answer":1
},
{
    "question":"Which of the following is correctly evaluated for this function?",
      "choice1":"(x**y) / z",
      "choice2":"(x / y) * z",
      "choice3":"(x**y) % z",
      "choice4": "(x / y) / z",
      "answer":3
},
{
    "question":"What will be the output of the following Python code?\n l=[1, 0, 2, 0, 'hello', '', []] \n list(filter(bool, l))",
      "choice1":"[1, 0, 2, ‘hello’, ”, []]",
      "choice2":"Error",
      "choice3":" [1, 0, 2, 0, ‘hello’, ”, []]",
      "choice4": "[1, 2, ‘hello’]",
      "answer":4
},
{
    "question":"Which of the following blocks will always be executed whether an exception is encountered or not in a program?" ,
       "choice1":"try" ,
       "choice2":"finally" ,
       "choice3": "except",
       "choice4":"None of these" ,
       "answer":2
},
   {
     "question":"Which of the following are valid escape sequences in Python?" ,
       "choice1":"\n" ,
       "choice2":"\t" ,
       "choice3": "\\",
       "choice4":"All of the above" ,
       "answer":4
},
 {
     "question":" What will be the output of the following Python code? \n class tester:\n def __init__(self, id): \n self.id = str(id)\n id='224' \n >>>temp = tester(12)>>>print(temp.id)" ,
       "choice1":"12" ,
       "choice2":"224" ,
       "choice3": "None",
       "choice4":"Error" ,
       "answer":1
},
{
    "question":"What will be the output of the following code snippet?\n print(2**3 + (5 + 6)**(1 + 1))" ,
       "choice1":"121" ,
       "choice2":"8" ,
       "choice3": "129",
       "choice4":"None of the above" ,
       "answer":1
}]